School of the Museum of Fine Arts Records UA133
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Audiovisual materials, 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011; 14.4 Linear Feet
  - Inka Essenhigh, 2008-11-25; UA133.011.080.00018 (Box 80)
    Essenhigh, Inka
  - Scott McCarney and Keith Smith lecture (1 of 2), 2014-04-10; UA133.011.080.00019 (Box 80)
    McCarney, Scott; Smith, Keith
  - Scott McCarney and Keith Smith lecture (2 of 2), 2014-04-10; UA133.011.080.00020 (Box 80)
  - Hilton Als - Hale Visiting Artist lecturer - SMFA Roundtable, 2014-03-07; UA133.011.080.00021 (Box 80)
    Als, Hilton
  - Carrie Moyer lecture, 2014-03-06; UA133.011.080.00022 (Box 80)
    Moyer, Carrie
  - Mary Reid Kelley and Patrick Kelley lecture, 2014-03-05; UA133.011.080.00023 (Box 80)
    Kelly, Mary Reid; Kelley, Patrick
  - William Villalongo lecture, 2014-04-17; UA133.011.080.00024 (Box 80)
    Villalongo, William
  - Zoe Beloff lecture, 2014-04-16; UA133.011.080.00025 (Box 80)
    Beloff, Zoe
  - Steve Dibenedetto lecture, 2013-02-07; UA133.011.080.00026 (Box 80)
    Dibenedetto, Steve
  - Sarah Malakoff lecture, 2013-09-26; UA133.011.080.00027 (Box 80)
    Malakoff, Sarah
  - Jorge Antonio Fernández-Torres lecture, 2013-09-10; UA133.011.080.00028 (Box 80)
    Fernández-Torres, Jorge Antonio
  - Bill Arning lecture, 2013-06-13; UA133.011.080.00029 (Box 80)
    Arning, Bill
  - Barnaby Furnas lecture, 2013-10-03; UA133.011.080.00030 (Box 80)
    Furnas, Barnaby
  - Four Sculptors - Heather Dewey - Hagborg Lecture, 2013-10-01; UA133.011.080.00031 (Box 80)
    Dewey, Heather
  - Henry Horenstein lecture, 2013-07-14; UA133.011.080.00032 (Box 80)
    Horenstein, Henry
  - Elijah Gowin lecture, 2013-10-10; UA133.011.080.00033 (Box 80)
    Gowin, Elijah
  - Julia Jacquette lecture, 2013-03-07; UA133.011.080.00034 (Box 80)
    Jacquette, Julia
  - Nayland Blake lecture, 2013-02-26; UA133.011.080.00035 (Box 80)
  - Eve Laramee lecture, 2013-11-19; UA133.011.080.00036 (Box 80)
    Laramee, Eve
  - Walid Radd lecture, 2013-04-18; UA133.011.080.00037 (Box 80)
    Radd, Walid
  - Henry Horenstein lecture, 2013-11-21; UA133.011.080.00038 (Box 80)
  - Latoya Ruby Frazier, 2013-03-14; UA133.011.080.00039 (Box 80)
    Frazier, Latoya Ruby
  - Andrea Geyer lecture, 2013-02-28; UA133.011.080.00040 (Box 80)
    Geyer, Andrea
  - Jackie Saccoccio lecture, 2013-10-31; UA133.011.080.00041 (Box 80)
    Saccoccio, Jackie
  - Donald Moffett lecture, 2013-11-14; UA133.011.080.00042 (Box 80)
    Moffett, Donald
  - Boulet (Gilles Roussel) lecture, 2013-04-10; UA133.011.080.00043 (Box 80)
    Roussel, Gilles; Boulet
  - Amy Stein lecture, 2013-10-24; UA133.011.080.00044 (Box 80)
    Stein, Amy
  - Wendy Jacob lecture, 2013-11-05; UA133.011.080.00045 (Box 80)
    Jacob, Wendy
  - Thomas Eggerer lecture, 2013-03-28; UA133.011.080.00046 (Box 80)
    Eggerer, Thomas
  - Annie Hann and Daniel Mihalyo (Lead Pencil Studio) lecture, 2013-04-02; UA133.011.080.00047 (Box 80)
    Hann, Annie; Mihalyo, Daniel
  - Fred Tomaselli lecture, 2013-04-11; UA133.011.080.00048 (Box 80)
    Tomaselli, Fred
  - 2013 Hale Lecturer: Matthew Day Jackson - round table discussion, 2013-04-04; UA133.011.080.00049 (Box 80)
    Jackson, Matthew Day
  - Antoniadis and Stone lecture, 2013-04-09; UA133.011.080.00050 (Box 80)
  - Steve Locke lecture, 2013-10-17; UA133.011.080.00051 (Box 80)
    Locke, Steve
  - Ben Rubin lecture, 2013-10-22; UA133.011.080.00052; Rubin, Ben (Box 80)
  - Daniel Rich lecture, 2012-09-27; UA133.011.080.00053 (Box 80)
    Rich, Daniel
  - Lecture, 2012-10-30; UA133.011.080.00054 (Box 80)
    Orta, Lucy; Orta, Jorge
  - Annette Lemieux lecture, 2012-11-01; UA133.011.080.00055 (Box 80)
    Lemieux, Annette
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2012-11-15; UA133.011.080.00056 (Box 80)
    Hancock, Trenton Doyle
  - Noritake Minima lecture, 2012-11-15; UA133.011.080.00057 (Box 80)
    Minima, Noritake
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2012-10-11; UA133.011.080.00058 (Box 80)
    Sprecher, Jared
  - Mohamed Abla lecture, 2012-02-21; UA133.011.080.00059 (Box 80)
    Abla, Mohamed
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2012-09-25; UA133.011.080.00060 (Box 80)
    Fasnacht, Heide
  - Emma Bowkett, 2012-04-19; UA133.011.080.00061 (Box 80)
    Bowkett, Emma
  - David Humphrey, 2012-04-12; UA133.011.080.00062 (Box 80)
    Humphrey, David
  - Beckwith Lecture - tape 1, 2012-09-19; UA133.011.080.00063 (Box 80)
    Roberts, Veronica
  - Beckwith Lecture - tape 2, 2012-09-19; UA133.011.080.00064 (Box 80)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2012-10-23; UA133.011.080.00065 (Box 80)
    Boroson, Lee
  - Tape 1 of 2, 2012-04-10; UA133.011.080.00066 (Box 80)
    Pierce, Leighton
  - Tape 2 of 2, 2012-04-10; UA133.011.080.00067 (Box 80)
  - Tape 1 of 2, 2012-03-06; UA133.011.080.00068 (Box 80)
    Geiser, Janie
  - Tape 2 of 2, 2012-03-06; UA133.011.080.00069 (Box 80)
  - Sue Vanderheck, 2012-02-16; UA133.011.080.00070 (Box 80)
    Vanderheck, Sue
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series, 2012-11-20; UA133.011.080.00071 (Box 80)
    Acosta, Scoli
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2012-10-18; UA133.011.080.00072 (Box 80)
    Rankin, Tom
  - Perry Bard lecture, 2012-09-20; UA133.011.080.00073 (Box 80)
    Bard, Perry
  - Tape 1 of 2, 2012-03-27; UA133.011.080.00074 (Box 80)
    Thornton, Leslie
  - Tape 2 of 2, 2012-03-27; UA133.011.080.00075 (Box 80)
  - John Divola, 2012-03-08; UA133.011.080.00076 (Box 80)
    Divola, John
  - Eileen Quinlan, 2012-03-29; UA133.011.080.00077 (Box 80)
    Quinlan, Eileen
  - Alison Elizabeth Taylor, 2012-03-15; UA133.011.080.00078 (Box 80)
    Taylor, Alison Elizabeth
  - Eric Fischl artist talk, 2007-01-23; UA133.011.080.00079 (Box 80)
    Fischl, Eric
  - Laida Lertxundi lecture (1 of 2), 2014-03-26; UA133.011.080.00080 (Box 80)
    Lertxundi, Laida
  - Laida Lertxundi lecture (2 of 2), 2014-03-26; UA133.011.080.00081 (Box 80)
  - Phillip Taaffe lecture (2 of 2), 2014-04-03; UA133.011.080.00082 (Box 80)
    Taaffe, Phillip
  - Manjari Sharma lecture, 2014-04-01; UA133.011.080.00083 (Box 80)
    Sharma, Manjari
  - Nina Katchadourian lecture, 2014-03-13; UA133.011.080.00084 (Box 80)
    Katchadourian, Nina
  - Dawit Petros lecture, 2014-02-27; UA133.011.080.00085 (Box 80)
    Petros, Dawit
  - Lisa Raskin lecture, 2014-02-25; UA133.011.080.00086 (Box 80)
    Raskin, Lisa
  - Daniel Bozhkov lecture, 2014-02-11; UA133.011.080.00087 (Box 80)
    Bozhkov, Daniel
  - Sage Sohier lecture, 2014-02-06; UA133.011.080.00088 (Box 80)
    Sohier, Sage
  - Gideon Bok lecture, 2014-01-30; UA133.011.080.00089 (Box 80)
    Bok, Gideon
  - William Powhida lecture, 2011-11-17; UA133.011.080.00090 (Box 80)
    Powhide, William
  - Angela Dufresne, 2011-10-13; UA133.011.080.00091 (Box 80)
    Dufresne, Angela
  - Claire Fontaine, 2011-11-15; UA133.011.080.00092 (Box 80)
    Fontaine, Claire
  - Franklin Evans, 2011-10-27; UA133.011.080.00093 (Box 80)
    Evans, Franklin
  - David Kelly lecture, 2011-11-03; UA133.011.080.00094 (Box 80)
    Kelley, David
  - Photography lecture, 2011-10-13; UA133.011.080.00095 (Box 80)
    Stanbridge, Andrew
  - Dan Peterman, 2011-11-22; UA133.011.080.00096 (Box 80)
    Peterman, Dan
  - Lorie Novak lecture, 2012-11-29; UA133.011.080.00097 (Box 80)
    Novak, Lorie
  - 5th Year artist talks, 2011-03-13; UA133.011.080.00098 (Box 80)
  - Nicole Cherubini, 2011-03-15; UA133.011.080.00099 (Box 80)
    Cherubini, Nicole
  - Dasha Shishkin, 2011-03-29; UA133.011.080.00100 (Box 80)
    Shishkin, Dasha
  - Erin Shirreff, 2011-04-14; UA133.011.080.00101 (Box 80)
    Shirreff, Erin
  - Bradley McCallum, 2011-03-10; UA133.011.080.00102 (Box 80)
    McCallum, Bradley
  - Daniel Dove, 2011-03-01; UA133.011.080.00103 (Box 80)
    Dove, Daniel
  - Emily Roysdon, 2011-02-17; UA133.011.080.00104 (Box 80)
    Roysdon, Emily
  - Matt Saunders, 2011-02-15; UA133.011.080.00105 (Box 80)
    Saunders, Matt
  - Student Artist Talks, 2011-02-14; UA133.011.080.00106 (Box 80)
  - Temporary Services, 2011-04-19; UA133.011.080.00107 (Box 80)
  - Patti Smith, 2011-03-16; UA133.011.080.00108 (Box 80)
    Smith, Patti
  - Tina Barney, 2011-03-31; UA133.011.080.00109 (Box 80)
    Barney, Tina
  - Tauba Auerbach, 2011-04-12; UA133.011.080.00110 (Box 80)
    Auerbach, Tauba
  - Alix Pearlstein, 2011-04-05; UA133.011.080.00111 (Box 80)
    Pearlstein, Alix
  - Tsiba Geva, 2010-04-06; UA133.011.080.00112 (Box 80)
    Geva, Tsiba
  - David Hilliard, 2010-10-28; UA133.011.080.00113 (Box 80)
    Hilliard, David
  - Jonathan Van Dyke, 2010-02-23; UA133.011.080.00114 (Box 80)
    Van Dyke, Jonathan
  - Jedediah Caesar, 2011; UA133.011.080.00115 (Box 80)
    Caesar, Jedediah
  - Jedediah Caesar, 2011-10-11; UA133.011.080.00116 (Box 80)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture (Tape 1), 2011-09-22; UA133.011.080.00117 (Box 80)
    Gupta & Fox
  - Visiting Artist Lecture (Tape 1), 2011-09-22; UA133.011.080.00118 (Box 80)
  - Warren Mather, 2010-09-23; UA133.011.080.00119 (Box 80)
    Mather, Warren
  - Neeta Madahar, 2010-09-23; UA133.011.080.00120 (Box 80)
    Madahar, Neeta
  - Mags Harries, 2010-09-20; UA133.011.080.00121 (Box 80)
  - Four Sculptors, 2010-02-09; UA133.011.080.00122 (Box 80)
    Herzog, Elena
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series (Tape 1), 2010-02-17; UA133.011.080.00123 (Box 80)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series (Tape 2), 2010-02-17; UA133.011.080.00124 (Box 80)
  - Four Photographers Lecture Series - Aziz+Cucher (Tape 1), 2010-03-16; UA133.011.080.00125 (Box 80)
    Aziz, Anthony; Cucher, Samuel
  - Four Photographers Lecture Series - Aziz+Cucher (Tape 2), 2010-03-16; UA133.011.080.00126 (Box 80)
  - Kate Gilmore (1 of 2), 2010-03-30; UA133.011.080.00127 (Box 80)
    Gilmore, Kate
  - Kendall Buster, 2010-01-13; UA133.011.080.00128 (Box 80)
    Buster, Kendall
  - Kendall Buster, 2010-04-13; UA133.011.080.00129 (Box 80)
  - Four Photographers Lecture Series - Part 1 of 2, 2010-02-11; UA133.011.080.00130 (Box 80)
    Drabble, Neil
  - Four Photographers Lecture Series - Part 2 of 2, 2010-02-11; UA133.011.080.00131 (Box 80)
  - Kurt Kauper (1 of 2), 2010-03-16; UA133.011.080.00132 (Box 80)
  - Kurt Kauper (2 of 2), 2010-03-16; UA133.011.080.00133 (Box 80)
  - Four Sculptors, 2010-02-09; UA133.011.080.00134 (Box 80)
  - Jennifer Dalton, 2010-09-21; UA133.011.080.00135 (Box 80)
  - Charline Von Heyl, 2010-09-28; UA133.011.080.00136 (Box 80)
    Heyle, Charline von
  - David Davison, 2010-09-29; UA133.011.080.00137 (Box 80)
  - Ridley Howard, 2010-10-26; UA133.011.080.00138 (Box 80)
    Howard, Ridley
  - Dana Frankfort, 2010-10-12; UA133.011.080.00139 (Box 80)
    Frankfort, Dana
  - Florencio Gelabert, 2010-10-05; UA133.011.080.00140 (Box 80)
    Gelabert, Florencio
  - Tsiba Geva, 2010-04-06; UA133.011.080.00141 (Box 80)
  - Tsiba Geva, 2010-04-06; UA133.011.080.00142 (Box 80)
  - Kate Gilmore (2 of 2), 2010-03-30; UA133.011.080.00143 (Box 80)
  - Michael Rees, 2010-11-29; UA133.011.080.00144 (Box 80)
    Rees, Michael
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2010-11-16; UA133.011.080.00145 (Box 80)
    Cuijanovic, Adam
  - Chris Verene, 2010-11-18; UA133.011.080.00146 (Box 80)
    Verene, Chris
  - Phoebe Washburn, 2009-09-10; UA133.011.080.00147 (Box 80)
    Washburn, Phoebe
  - Wendy White, 2009-03-24; UA133.011.080.00148 (Box 80)
    White, Wendy
  - Tape 1 of 2, 2009-09-24; UA133.011.080.00149 (Box 80)
    Collins, Michael
  - Tape 2 of 2, 2009-09-24; UA133.011.080.00150 (Box 80)
  - Sanford Biggers, 2009-10-13; UA133.011.080.00151 (Box 80)
    Biggers, Sanford
  - Josephine Halvorson, 2009-09-29; UA133.011.080.00152 (Box 80)
    Halvorson, Josephine
  - Combat Print, 2009-09-17; UA133.011.080.00153 (Box 80)
    Combat Print
  - Brad Kahlhamer, 2009-02-24; UA133.011.080.00154 (Box 80)
    Kahlhamer, Brad
  - Danne Cooper, 2009-02-17; UA133.011.080.00155 (Box 80)
    Cooper, Danne
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2009-02-10; UA133.011.080.00156 (Box 80)
    Gonzales, Wayne
  - Taryn Simon, 2009-02-12; UA133.011.080.00157 (Box 80)
    Simon, Taryn
  - Lalla Essaydi, 2009-01-22; UA133.011.080.00158 (Box 80)
    Essaydi, Lalla
  - Wendy Jacobs, 2009-09-14; UA133.011.080.00159 (Box 80)
    Jacobs, Wendy
  - Laurel Nakadate, 2009-11-18; UA133.011.080.00160 (Box 80)
  - Wangech Mutu, 2009-04-14; UA133.011.080.00161 (Box 80)
    Mutu, Wangech
  - Dana Schutz, 2009-04-09; UA133.011.080.00162 (Box 80)
    Schutz, Dana
  - Jason Middlebrook, 2009-03-31; UA133.011.080.00163 (Box 80)
    Middlebrook, Jason
  - Jason Middlebrook, 2009-03-31; UA133.011.080.00164 (Box 80)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2009-11-17; UA133.011.080.00165 (Box 80)
    Driscoll, Ellen
  - Chie Fueki, 2009-11-10; UA133.011.080.00166 (Box 80)
    Fueki, Chie
  - Moyra Davey, 2009-11-04; UA133.011.080.00167 (Box 80)
    Davey, Moyra
  - Beverly Semmes, 2009-10-27; UA133.011.080.00168 (Box 80)
    Semmes, Beverly
  - Karl Baden, 2009-10-22; UA133.011.080.00169 (Box 80)
    Baden, Karl
  - Hamra Abbas, 2009-10-20; UA133.011.080.00170 (Box 80)
    Abbas, Hamra
  - Nina Katchadourian, 2008-04-08; UA133.011.080.00171 (Box 80)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2008-02-26; UA133.011.080.00172 (Box 80)
    Wodiczko, Krzysztof
  - Esteban Pastorino, 2008-04-03; UA133.011.080.00173 (Box 80)
    Pastorino, Esteban
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2008-04-01; UA133.011.080.00174 (Box 80)
    Kojo, Daniel
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2008-03-25; UA133.011.080.00175 (Box 80)
    Sze, Sarah
  - Cory Archangel, 2008-02-13; UA133.011.080.00176 (Box 80)
    Archangel, Cory
  - Four Photographers Lecture Series, 2008-01-31; UA133.011.080.00177 (Box 80)
    Angulo, Liliana
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2008-01-30; UA133.011.080.00178 (Box 80)
    Pecou, Fahamu
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2008-01-29; UA133.011.080.00179 (Box 80)
    Greenwold, Mark
  - MFA, Riley Auditorium, 2008-09-25; UA133.011.080.00180 (Box 80)
    Ebner, Shannon
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2008-04-15; UA133.011.080.00181 (Box 80)
    Reichek, Elaine
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2008-02-28; UA133.011.080.00182 (Box 80)
    Flynn, Bill
  - Four Photographers Lecture Series, 2007-11-15; UA133.011.080.00183 (Box 80)
    O'Hare Slavick, Elen
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2007-11-13; UA133.011.080.00184 (Box 80)
    Robleto, Dario
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2007-10-30; UA133.011.080.00185 (Box 80)
    Sherman, Kelly
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2007-10-23; UA133.011.080.00186 (Box 80)
    Navarro, Ivan
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2007-10-16; UA133.011.080.00187 (Box 80)
    Gallagher, Sheila
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture Series, 2007-03-13; UA133.011.080.00188 (Box 80)
    Tallichet, Jude
  - Eighth Painters, 2007-03-27; UA133.011.080.00189 (Box 80)
    Linhares, Judith
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2007-09-11; UA133.011.080.00190 (Box 80)
    Van Tran, Tam
  - M. Bakowitz, 2007-09-06; UA133.011.080.00191 (Box 80)
    Bakowitz, M.
  - Eight Painters Lecture Series, 2007-04-10; UA133.011.080.00192 (Box 80)
    Ezawa, Kota
  - Petherbridge, 2007-03-12; UA133.011.080.00193 (Box 80)
    Petherbridge, Deanna
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2007-10-10; UA133.011.080.00194 (Box 80)
    Banai, Noit
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2007-09-18; UA133.011.080.00195 (Box 80)
    Janney, Chris
  - Eight Photographers Lecture Series, 2007-09-20; UA133.011.080.00196 (Box 80)
    Morrissey, Trish
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2007-09-26; UA133.011.080.00197 (Box 80)
    Donohue, Bonnie
  - Eight Painters Lecture, 2007-10-02; UA133.011.080.00198 (Box 80)
    Griffin, Rashawn
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture Series, 2007-10-09; UA133.011.080.00199 (Box 80)
    Ford, Kianga
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture Series, 2007-02-06; UA133.011.080.00200 (Box 80)
    Rakowitz, Michael
  - Eight Painters Lecture, 2007-02-13; UA133.011.080.00201 (Box 80)
    Hammond, Jane
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2007-03-02; UA133.011.080.00202 (Box 80)
    Sibley, Donald
  - Four Sculptures Lecture Series, 2007-03-06; UA133.011.080.00203 (Box 80)
    Olivier, Karen
  - Amy Wilson, 2006-10-10; UA133.011.080.00204 (Box 80)
    Wilson, Amy
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2004-11-03; UA133.011.080.00205 (Box 80)
    Leveque, Les
  - Magdalena Campos-Pons, 2004-09-29; UA133.011.080.00206 (Box 80)
    Campos-Pons, Magdalena
  - Primordial Godspeed, 2004; UA133.011.080.00207 (Box 80)
  - Medal Award dinner, 1999; UA133.011.080.00208 (Box 80)
  - Lecture and mobile exhibition, 1992-10-15; UA133.011.080.00209 (Box 80)
    Bolton, Richard
  - Jonathan Lasker, 1991-04-03; UA133.011.080.00210 (Box 80)
    Lasker, Jonathan
  - Race in Media symposium, circa 1998; UA133.011.080.00211 (Box 80)
  - 5th Year 1992 (raw footage), 1992-01-01; UA133.011.080.00212 (Box 80)
  - Gallery Talk, 1997-11-14; UA133.011.080.00213 (Box 80)
    Jones, Ron; Stein, Laura
  - Jerry Saltz, 1995-04-05; UA133.011.080.00214 (Box 80)
    Saltz, Jerry
  - Esther Anderson, 1998; UA133.011.080.00215 (Box 80)
    Anderson, Esther
  - Matt Hogan lecture, 1985-11-06; UA133.011.080.00216 (Box 80)
    Hogan, Matt
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series, 1988-03-17; UA133.011.080.00217 (Box 80)
    Connors, Maureen
  - Michael Tracy lecture, 1988-02-04; UA133.011.080.00218 (Box 80)
    Tracy, Michael
  - Paul Laffoley lecture, 1987-10-08; UA133.011.080.00219 (Box 80)
    Laffoley, Paul
  - Marianna Pineda, 1991-02-28; UA133.011.080.00220 (Box 80)
    Pineda, Marianna
  - Nancy Azara, circa 1990 -- 1999; UA133.011.080.00221 (Box 80)
    Azara, Nancy
  - Elizabeth Murray, 1990-10-05; UA133.011.080.00222 (Box 80)
    Murray, Elizabeth
  - Paleolithic, 1990-10-11; UA133.011.080.00223 (Box 80)
    Harrod, James
  - The Connection, 1998-10-16; UA133.011.080.00224 (Box 80)
    Danto, Arthur C.
  - New Territory Symposium, 1990-11-10; UA133.011.080.00225 (Box 80)
  - New Territory Symposium, 1990-11-09; UA133.011.080.00226 (Box 80)
  - Anne Truitt, 1988-08-08; UA133.011.080.00227 (Box 80)
  - Anne Truitt, 1988-08-08; UA133.011.080.00228 (Box 80)
  - Act of Watching/ Network of Letters/ Green Silk/ Sensitive Bones, circa 1990 -- 1999; UA133.011.080.00229 (Box 80)
    Zweig, Ellen
  - Bob Flanigan, 1995-01-01; UA133.011.080.00230 (Box 80)
    Flanigan, Bob
  - Gallery Talk, 1997-09-01; UA133.011.080.00231 (Box 80)
    Stein, Laura
  - Art systems training, circa 1990 -- 1999; UA133.011.080.00232 (Box 80)
  - Nauman packing procedure, circa 1990 -- 1999; UA133.011.080.00233 (Box 80)
    Nauman, Bruce
  - Project, circa 1990 -- 1999; UA133.011.080.00234 (Box 80)
  - 125 anniversary, 1996-01-01; UA133.011.080.00235 (Box 80)
    Ellsworth, Kelly
  - Fred Joe Ansly, 1998-01-01; UA133.011.080.00236 (Box 80)
    Ansly, Fred Joe
  - Gallery Talk - "Pause-Still", 1998-02-13; UA133.011.080.00237 (Box 80)
  - Collins Milazzo, 1989-11-18; UA133.011.080.00238 (Box 80)
    Milazzo, Collins
  - Eve Laramee, 1990-01-25; UA133.011.080.00239 (Box 80)
  - Eve Laramee, 1989-02-03; UA133.011.080.00240 (Box 80)
  - Frog Prince - lecture excerpt; art exchange, 1984; UA133.011.080.00241 (Box 80)
  - Marlon Riggs symp, circa 1980 -- 1989; UA133.011.080.00242 (Box 80)
    Riggs, Marlon
  - Ralph Helmick, 1991-01-31; UA133.011.080.00243 (Box 80)
    Helmick, Ralph
  - Gene Highstein, 1989-01-26; UA133.011.080.00244 (Box 80)
    Highstein, Gene
  - The Guerilla Girls, 1989-01-30; UA133.011.080.00245 (Box 80)
    Guerrilla Girls (Group of artists)
  - Guerilla Girls, 1989-01-30; UA133.011.080.00246 (Box 80)
  - Mia Westerlund Roosen, 1989-02-23; UA133.011.080.00247 (Box 80)
    Roosen, Mia Westerlund
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series teacher, 1989-03-09; UA133.011.080.00248 (Box 80)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1989-03-09; UA133.011.080.00249 (Box 80)
  - Arthur C. Danto, 1989-03-13; UA133.011.080.00250 (Box 80)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1989-01-25; UA133.011.080.00251 (Box 80)
    Oppenheim, Dennis
  - Lauren Ewing, 1989-09-27; UA133.011.080.00252 (Box 80)
    Ewing, Lauren
  - John Baldessari, 1989-10-30; UA133.011.080.00253 (Box 80)
    Baldessari, John
  - Mary Kelly, 1988-12-01; UA133.011.080.00254 (Box 80)
    Kelly, Mary Reid
  - Jill Johnston, 1988-11-07; UA133.011.080.00255 (Box 80)
    Johnston, Jill, 1929-2010
  - Faculty panel discussion, 1988-11-03; UA133.011.080.00256 (Box 80)
    Sloan, Sandy; Arsen, Marilyn; Davidson, David; Seigfreid, Haly; MacDonald, Bruce
  - Nancy Spero at SMFA, 1988-10-20; UA133.011.080.00257 (Box 80)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1989-10-19; UA133.011.080.00258 (Box 80)
    Acconci, Vito
  - Vito Acconci, 1989-10-19; UA133.011.080.00259 (Box 80)
  - Frog Prince - lecture excerpt; art exchange, 1984; UA133.011.080.00260 (Box 80)
  - Carolee Schneemann, 1988-02-22; UA133.011.080.00261 (Box 80)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series, 1988-03-17; UA133.011.080.00262 (Box 80)
  - Medal award dinner '97, 1997-01-01; UA133.011.080.00263 (Box 80)
    Goldin, Nan
  - Faculty meeting, circa 1980 -- 1999; UA133.011.080.00264 (Box 80)
    Rogers, Malcolm
  - Music of Larry Johnson - on the origin of Information, 1988; UA133.011.080.00265 (Box 80)
  - Joel Fisher, 1990-03-01; UA133.011.080.00266 (Box 80)
    Fisher, Joel
  - Robert Lobe, 1990-10-18; UA133.011.080.00267 (Box 80)
    Lobe, Robert
  - Nancy Graves, 1988-11-16; UA133.011.080.00268 (Box 80)
    Graves, Nancy
  - TODT, 1990-02-13; UA133.011.080.00269 (Box 80)
  - Debby Malcolm, 1997-04-02; UA133.011.080.00270 (Box 80)
    Debby, Malcolm
  - New Territory, 1990-11-10; UA133.011.080.00271 (Box 80)
  - Illegible: "Mosaics/Equinox/Face Flow", 1987; UA133.011.080.00272 (Box 80)
  - Robert Wise, 1991-03-08; UA133.011.080.00273 (Box 80)
  - Barbara Kruger, circa 1980 -- 1999; UA133.011.080.00274 (Box 80)
  - New Territory Symposium, 1990-11-10; UA133.011.080.00275 (Box 80)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1989-11-02; UA133.011.080.00276 (Box 80)
    Casebere, James
  - Paul Benny, 2001-03-14; UA133.011.080.00277 (Box 80)
    Benny, Paul
  - Call in's from public - reflection of show on NPR w/ Mr. Rogers, circa 1980 -- 1999; UA133.011.080.00278 (Box 80)
    Ritti, Herb; Rogers, Fred
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1995-11-02; UA133.011.081.00001 (Box 81)
    Mitchell, Curtis
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1994-11-01; UA133.011.081.00002 (Box 81)
    Antony, Janine
  - Bob Flanagan, 1995; UA133.011.081.00003 (Box 81)
    Flanagan, Bob
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1994-10-20; UA133.011.081.00004 (Box 81)
    Webster, Meg
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1994-11-04; UA133.011.081.00005 (Box 81)
    Coffey, Susanna
  - Edie Bresler, 1995-03-02; UA133.011.081.00006 (Box 81)
    Bresler, Edie
  - Beckwith Lecture, 1995-11-02; UA133.011.081.00007 (Box 81)
    Viola, Bill
  - Panel talk, 1995-11-30; UA133.011.081.00008 (Box 81)
    The Boston School.
  - Stan Brakhage Beckwith Lecture, 1996-01-01; UA133.011.081.00009 (Box 81)
    Brakhage, Stan
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1994-10-06; UA133.011.081.00010 (Box 81)
    Yarde, Richard
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1995-11-01; UA133.011.081.00011 (Box 81)
    Plimack, Sylvia
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1995-09-28; UA133.011.081.00012 (Box 81)
    Butler, Tom
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1995-09-22; UA133.011.081.00013 (Box 81)
    Ferrandini, Bob
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1995-08-08; UA133.011.081.00014 (Box 81)
    Zwack, Michael
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1997-10-02; UA133.011.081.00015 (Box 81)
    Hoke, Lisa
  - Jerry Saltz, 1997-09-25; UA133.011.081.00016 (Box 81)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1997-09-26; UA133.011.081.00017 (Box 81)
    Bamber, Judie
  - Wolf Kahn, 1999-01-25; UA133.011.081.00018 (Box 81)
    Kahn, Wolf
  - Beckwith Lecture, 1994-10-13; UA133.011.081.00019 (Box 81)
    Kaprow, Allan
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1999-01-29; UA133.011.081.00020 (Box 81)
    Luckacks, Attila Richards
  - Four Painters Lecture, 1994-09-30; UA133.011.081.00021 (Box 81)
    Cumming, Robert
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1995-02-02; UA133.011.081.00022 (Box 81)
    Cogswell, Margaret
  - Medal awards dinner 1999, 1999-01-01; UA133.011.081.00023 (Box 81)
    Glimcher, Arne; Glimcher, Milly